(Howard's Mother(voice):)Fly for God's sake.
HOWARD:
Fine, I'll stay. You happy, crazy lady?
(Howard(voice):)I sure as hell hope so,
because you're ruining my life!
[DOOR SLAMS]
(Leonard(into phone):)Hey, Penny, it's Leonard. Good news,
you can take your head out of the oven.
(Sheldon(removing hernia support):)I guess I won't be needing this.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
(Sheldon:)The new ones.
[IN SINGSONG VOICE]
They're here.
(Leonard:)Stay calm.
We don't know anything about them yet.
[OBJECTS RATTLING]
(Leonard:)- What are you doing?
- I'm checking for musical instruments.
(Sheldon:)Does that sound like castanets to you?
The box says "kitchen."
(Sheldon:)So? Do cocaine smugglers
write "cocaine" on the box?
- Hello?
- Hello.